Contact

brandonsterling08@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/brandonsterling-ms-aprn-agacnp-bcccrn-817b5940 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing
Critical Care
Post Anesthesia Care

Languages

English

Brandon Sterling, MS, APRN, AGACNP-BC, CCRN

APRN ICU at MD Anderson Cancer Center Houston, Texas

Summary

Board Certified Adult Gerontology Acute Care Nurse Practitioner dedicated to engaging my abilities and talents to develop, analyze, and translate knowledge through commitment to excellence, inquiry, collaboration, professionalism and accountability. As a selfless, driven professional leader with a pledge to delivering evidenced-based, quality care I am devoted to fostering a culture of education, research, efficiency, and diversity.

Experience

MD Anderson Cancer Center 4 years 9 months

APRNICU

July 2018 - Present (2 years)

Houston, Texas Area

I manage critically ill patients in medical and surgical ICU where responsibilities include interdisciplinary rounds, advanced care planning, participating in department and institutional initiatives and line insertions.

APRN Department of Urology, Inpatient Services October 2015 - Present (4 years 9 months)

Harris Health System
Staff Nurse
May 2013 - October 2015 (2 years 6 months)

St. Luke's Episcopal Hospital Staff Nurse May 2008 - June 2013 (5 years 2 months)

Staff Nurse in cardiac intensive care units. Efficient and prudent patient care of patients requiring intra-aortic balloon pumps (IABP), pulmonary artery catheters (PA caths), continuous renal replacement therapy (CRRT),

therapeutic hypothermia, discontinuation of arterial and venous sheaths, and peripheral thrombolysis. As a medical cardiac unit our patient population include acute coronary syndromes, congestive heart failure, cardiac arrest, cardiomyopathy, respiratory failure, renal failure, severe peripheral vascular disease, pre hear transplant and pre ventricular device patients.

AMN Healthcare
Travel Nurse
April 2010 - April 2011 (1 year 1 month)
Del Mar California

Travel nurse in Temple TX, New York NY, Riverside CA, Torrance CA

Education

Texas Woman's University

Doctor of Philosophy - PhD · (2017 - 2023)

Texas Woman's University

Master of Science (M.S.), Acute Care Nurse Practioner · (2013 - 2015)

The University of Texas at Austin BSN, Nursing · (2004 - 2008)